(Sheldon:)for a long period of time
might attract the attention
(Sheldon:)of the hotel detective?
(Leonard:)If we do,
(Leonard:)we'll just tell him
to "hit the bricks, see?"
(Sheldon:)Seems a little confrontational,
but all right.
(Penny:)You know,
we won't be very far
(Sheldon:)from Skywalker Ranch.
(Leonard:)Oh, that's true.
(Leonard:)It's not like
we can get in there.
(Sheldon:)Why not?
I-I don't think George Lucas
put his headquarters
(Leonard:)in the middle of nowhere because
he wanted people dropping in.
(Sheldon:)Yoda's swamp was
in the middle of nowhere.
(Sheldon:)Tatooine was in the middle
of nowhere.
(Sheldon:)Hoth was in the middle
(Sheldon:)That's code, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)He wants us
to drop in.
(Leonard:)We do have time.
(Leonard:)I mean, we could drive by
and just look at it.
Yes! Oh...
(Sheldon:)I'm so excited.
(Sheldon:)And I just can't hide it.
"I'm about to lose control,
and I think I like it."